Md. Atikul Islam Romon FRONT END DEVELOPER

+8801729105192

islam.atik15@gmail.com github.com/atikulislamatik linkedin.com/in/atikul-islam-romon

Prottoy 12/a Raynagor Sylhet 3100, Bangladesh

Skilled & motivated developer with around 2+ years of hands-on development experience. To obtain a responsible and challenging Front End Developer position where my education and work experience will have valuable application.

EXPERIENCE

Digitizefit LLC, New York USA | 2022- Present

FRONT END DEVELOPER

- Built interactive single-page Next js app
- · Developed SPA using Rest API
- Utilize Html, CSS, and Javascript to create 10+ responsive landing pages for both company and client

OrderVox Limited , Portsmouth, UK | 2021-2022

FRONT END DEVELOPER

- Design and develop some themes for the client end and also an admin panel.
- · Redesign existing branding website for Ordere.
- Design and develop websites for clients.
- Manage website development projects from initial design through completion optimizing all cross-browser and multi-platform compatibility.

Salah Software Solution | 2020 - 2021

FRONT END DEVELOPER

• I've worked at ThemeForest Base Products, where worked with many IT professionals to accomplish team objects.

DEVELOPMENT

- https://surma.vercel.app/
- https://c3nft.vercel.app/
- https://anft.vercel.app/
- https://templates.hibootstrap.com/paso/default/index.html
- https://templates.hibootstrap.com/edvi/default/index.html
- · https://atikulislamatik.github.io/art/
- https://m.darun.app/

EDUCATION

BSC (Engg) in Computer Science & Engineering (2016-2020)

CGPA - 3.45

Metropolitan University, Sylhet

ORGANISATIONAL SKILLS

- Workshop on Front-end Web Development
- Intra MU Tech Emulation V1 Summer 2018
- Workshop on IoT

SKILLS

Languages

 $\mathsf{HTML}\,,\mathsf{CSS}\,,\mathsf{SCSS}\,,\mathsf{Javascript}\,,\mathsf{PHP}$

Framework

Bootstrap, Tailwindcss, Next Js

Libraries

React, Jquery

Others

Figma, Wordpress, Github, Git

• Experienced in using REST APIs

DEVELOPMENT

- http://ordere.co.uk/
- · https://paso-react-atik.netlify.app/
- https://atikulislamatik.github.io/Estate